<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<!--
	Copyright (c) 2008 Narciso Jaramillo
	All rights reserved.

	Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without 
	modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions are met:

    * Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright notice, 
      this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.
    * Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright 
      notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in the 
      documentation and/or other materials provided with the distribution.
    * Neither the name of Narciso Jaramillo nor the names of other 
      contributors may be used to endorse or promote products derived from 
      this software without specific prior written permission.

	THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND CONTRIBUTORS "AS IS" 
	AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE 
	IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE 
	DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE COPYRIGHT OWNER OR CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE 
	FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL 
	DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR 
	SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER 
	CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY,
	OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE 
	USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.
-->

<hints>
	<hint>
		<title>Tip #1: How do I get Snackr out of my way?</title>
		<description>
			<![CDATA[
				<p>There are a few ways to get Snackr out of the way:</p>
				<ul>
					<li>Right-click or ctrl-click on the ticker, or click the collapse arrow button on the tab, to collapse it. Click the collapse button again to uncollapse</li>
					<li>"Toss" Snackr to a different side of the screen or onto another monitor by dragging it a little ways and letting go. You can also set this manually in the Preferences tab of the Options popup.</li>
					<li>In the Preferences tab of the Options popup, turn off "always on top".</li>					
				</ul>
			]]>
		</description>
	</hint>
	<hint>
		<title>Tip #2: How come I'm not seeing some items from my feeds?</title>
		<description>
			<![CDATA[
				<p>There are a few reasons why you might not see items:</p>
				<ul>
					<li>By default, Snackr doesn't show items older than 30 days ago. You can adjust this in the Preferences tab of the Options popup.</li>					
					<li>Once you read an item, it never shows up again.</li>
					<li>Snackr shows unread items from a given feed in reverse order. If you don't read an item, it will eventually cycle back around.</li>
					<li>There might be a bug! If you feel like you're never seeing items from a feed, <a href="mailto:nj@snackr.net">send the feed URL to me</a> and I'll take a look at it.</li>
				</ul>
			]]>
		</description>
	</hint>
	<hint>
		<title>Tip #3: How can I quickly add a feed?</title>
		<description>
			<![CDATA[
				<p>There are several ways to add a feed:</p>
				<ul>
					<li>From Firefox on Windows, you can set Snackr as your main RSS feed reader. Click on a feed icon on a website, then from the dropdown at the top, choose "Choose Application...",
					   and browse to the Snackr application in Program Files. 
					   From then on, when you hit Subscribe, Snackr will automatically add the feed. You can also check the "Always use Snackr to subscribe to feeds" to make Firefox
					   add feeds to Snackr as soon as you
					   click on a feed icon. (Unfortunately, Firefox on Mac doesn't seem to support this workflow properly at the moment.)</li>
					<li>If you're mouse-oriented, copy the site or feed URL to the clipboard, then click the + button on the feed ticker. (Snackr will auto-discover feeds from websites if they have autodiscovery set up.)</li>
					<li>If you're keyboard-oriented, copy the URL, Alt-Tab/Cmd-Tab to the Snackr window, then hit Ctrl-V/Cmd-V to paste the feed.</li>
				</ul>
			]]>
		</description>
	</hint>
	<hint>
		<title>Tip #4: Snackr is cool, but it would be so much better if...</title>
		<description>
			<![CDATA[
				<p>Got a great idea for Snackr? <a href="mailto:nj@snackr.net">Send it to me!</a></p>
			]]>
		</description>
	</hint>
	<hint>
		<title>Tip #5: Where can I get more Snackr news?</title>
		<description>
			<![CDATA[
				<p>You can follow <a href="http://twitter.com/snackr">snackr</a> on twitter, or check the
				   <a href="http://rictus.com/muchado/category/Snackr/">Snackr category</a> on my blog, 
				   <a href="http://rictus.com/muchado">much ado about something</a>.</p>
			]]>
		</description>
	</hint>
</hints>